You're spending money every month
to make your phone ring.
Google ads. Local service ads.
Yard signs. Door hangers. Social.
And when that phone finally rings,
nobody picks up.
That's not a marketing problem.
That's a MONEY problem.
The average HVAC company misses 30%
of inbound calls during peak season.
Average ticket: $400 per call.
Ad spend: $30 to $50 per lead.
Every missed call costs you
the lead spend PLUS the job.
That's $80 to $450 gone,
every time nobody answers.
Every time your phone rings
and nobody picks up.
Meanwhile, your competitor's truck
is pulling into that driveway.
YOUR trucks are sitting.
YOUR techs are waiting.
YOUR schedule has gaps.
HVAC emergencies don't happen
at nine in the morning.
They happen at ten at night.
In July.
104 degrees outside,
and a family's AC just died.
No answer? They call the next company.
Evolve AI Agents from Intelligent Voice AI
answers every call.
Books the job.
Dispatches your tech.
And follows up on every missed lead.
24 hours a day. 7 days a week.
Your trucks stay busy.
Your techs stay productive.
Your revenue stops leaking.
Visit getivai.com/hvac
Stop paying for leads
your phone never answers.